{
    "id": "04361dd305aa4f11a752728cd5fce54f",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………. I was searching for a book, I came across this old photograph.",
            "description": "While shows time. It is used to talk about two actions or situations that happen simultaneously. ",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "While",
                "Whereas"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f9546f9204441299a95f48b27768137"
        },
        {
            "question": "They live ……………………. the climate is good.",
            "description": "Where is a relative adverb indicating place. It can connect two clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "where",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4d78305cef974ae58435e492513ee180"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the hotel …………………. our meetings used to take place.",
            "description": "Where means in which or at which.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33410f14b280475c8778c5744de3fdad"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ……………………. watch had been stolen complained to the police.",
            "description": "Whose is a possessive word.",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "which",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "439a95b69c0f4b7ba9ca3cb5224db299"
        },
        {
            "question": "The weather …………………….. fine we went out for a walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "been",
                "being"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e99df83ccc52490fb22affa69e63a078"
        },
        {
            "question": "The germ is ………………….. small to be seen with the naked eye.",
            "description": "Note the pattern too...to...",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b15ae1f09b684c9492629bb305982a16"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… his poor health, he attends the office regularly.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition. It is used before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "58c712589ee449b7826a65de154b4371"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. on tip-toe, he reached for the apple.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Stood",
                "Standing",
                "Having standing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4eda150316da440d829417f660bb5169"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. she got the message, she started for home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner",
                "As long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ddd35ebb088c4399b58d1fecdd3beee3"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. he is working, he should not be disturbed.",
            "description": "All of these words show reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Since",
                "Because",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "b6ff563aeb40465aad3ccb3cd9aa3f6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner had Venu arrived ……………………. his mother followed.",
            "description": "No sooner is a comparative expression use than after it.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "than",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06845140e79a401f88d737adda57eb2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He tip-toed into the room ……………………. he should disturb the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lest",
                "because",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0be7effbdc744908a191a6b005952c04"
        }
    ]
}